timesasia.net 2010-04-04

# Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at Times Asia. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.  
**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our news articles via e-mail, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these communications is provided.  
**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. DWB use cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. You can choose not to accept cookies by modifying your browser settings. At any time, you may remove any cookie stored on your hard drive by deleting them in your browser’s settings section.  
**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
**Advertisers and Affliates**  
DWB uses outside ad companies to display ads on this website. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to these information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, Nuffnang Philippines, Chitika and Infolinks. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.  
**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.**  
**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us here. Or you can send an e-mail directly to the editor: adam(at)timesasia.net
